babeeni.com 2019-02-03

# Privacy policy

At BABEENI  our excellent customer service always respect your privacy. Any personal information we collect is only used to fulfill your order. **We will not sell, rent, trade or share the information you provide with any different parties**. We will not contact you by telephone unless it is necessary to efficiently fulfill your order. If you become our members, you may receive emails from us to guide, supply some information such as special discounts or other promotions. Please take a few minutes to read and understand our privacy policies so that you are aware of how we collect and use your personal information.  

If you have any question or concern about our privacy policies, please contact us via customer@babeeni.com

 **Personal Information we will collect:**

BABEENI collects personal information to provide necessary for you to help you make the best orders. We also use your personal information to inform special promotions and contact you easily.

Customer's personal information is the information that directly associate with an personal identification (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, demographic information (date of birth, age and gender), payment information (including credit card numbers or online payment services numbers, financial information such as bank account numbers, purchase history and location information).

 **We use the Personal Information we collected for the following purposes:**

1\. For our daily management purpose such as establishing and managing your account, responding to your inquiries and feedback.

2\. To provide necessary information about our business, supply information of requested products and services; offer our newest products or services to you.
